She wiped some urine.
彼女が少し尿を拭きました
I'm already healed.
私はすでに治ったのです
i to you
私はあなたに
Even if it heals.
治 っても
You don't hit me.
あ なた は 私に当たらない
I heal you
私はあなたに治
Please say that.
って ください
and...
そして...
me haa
私 はあ
Aim for your legs...
なた の脚を向かって...
what?
何?
I'm heading for your legs...
私はあなたの脚を向かって...
This feels good.
これ気持ちいいね
Please take care of it.
手つけてください
Please raise your knees.
膝を上げてください
Please raise the top and bottom.
上下を上げてください
Please raise your legs.
足を上げてください
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Does it feel good around here?
この辺が気持ちいいですか?
Please leave it as is.
このまま出してください
Please take it outside.
外に出してください
I have a pain in my stomach.
お腹が痛いです
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいですか?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん